Thank you for watching!
Boom!
Here we go!
This is BananaOn, located on the 4th floor of the Nogizaka School office.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
I'm Nogizaka-chan!
This is Nogizaka-chan!
Yay!
A little bit, a little bit, a little bit
Seino
Yes!
The project we're doing today
please!
Let's go!
Akimoto Manatsu Graduation Memorial Legendary Hit Project
Congratulations!
Well, speaking of Akimoto... Akimoto is the history of Nogizaka.
Isn't that right?
I want to show everyone what I've done... or rather, I want to do something that sums it up.
Celebrating the graduation of Manatsu Akimoto's last project... and going on to become a legend.
Oh...
What is Akimoto's last project in Nogizaka Kenkenchu?
I'd like to work with a legend.
Legend, please come in.
No, no, no.
Oh, the legend's already here.
No, he's here, Ms. Manatsu.
Yes, I'm here.
Thank you very much.
Outrageous... Outrageous...
You know, she was called the Manatsu-san of Nogizaka.
Yes, sir
I'll be right back.
I was called the Degawa of Nogizaka.
I couldn't miss it since Manatsu-san was graduating.
Akimoto has been talking about his respect for Degawa on the show
Akimoto's last wish was not for a big hit, but for a dream.
Akimoto's last wish was to perform with the man of her dreams.
Murase-san, it's true, you've said a lot of things about wanting to meet that Deka-san, haven't you?
But in the past year or two, when we've met on other stations, on other shows, you've never said anything like that.
No, no, no, last year we met a couple of times, but nothing like that.
There's nothing funny about that, Murase-san.
What's the last project Akimoto, the Business Dekawa Girl, wants to do?
Here it is.
I like it.
Nice.
As expected of Ms. Tsuchiya.
This is Ms. Tsuchiya's Dekawa.
She's not here.
I don't know.
I don't get it.
And now, to the legend, Manatsu Akimoto's last car stunt.
Car Stands
Akimoto has challenged herself in a variety of grueling projects up until now.
As the culmination of her efforts, this time she would like to try her hand at the pinnacle of reaction art.
She wants to challenge a car stunt, the pinnacle of reaction art.
Well, if you want to do it, of course I will support you.
I think car stunts are dangerous and risky.
I think it's difficult as a reaction.
First of all, I'd like to know how to do a car stunt before doing a car stunt.
I'd like to see your aptitude for it.
Before car stunts, the pinnacle of reaction art
I don't know how to do it, but I'm going to learn how to do it.
First of all
I wonder what's in the box.
It doesn't matter.
Here we go again this week.
I wonder what's in the box.
What's in the box this week?
We've got something for you inside.
Wow!
What?
That looks amazing.
It's great.
Instruments.
Mayu-san
Musical Instrument
What is a musical instrument?
Please put your eyes on it.
What?
Oh, a musical instrument!
They're similar.
You're the same, Mayu.
You're the same.
What?
There, with the instrument.
They'll bite you.
What?
Where?
He's on the right side.
He's right there.
On the right hand side.
Wow.
Oh, wow.
Oh, nice.
That's nice.
Oh, wait a minute.Oh, wait a minute.
Wow.
eh?
Wait a minute.
It's okay, Mayu.
You're moving a lot.
Yes, every time I touch it.
She's so energetic.
Wow.
Ew.
eh?
Yes
I think I might have figured it out.
what is it?
Clouds.
That's great.
What?
Oh, wow.
That's amazing.
Put your hand in there and see what happens.
It's a scary toy.
Oh, my God.
That's amazing!
It was a moving toy.
Yes, yes, it was a moving toy.
It was a moving toy!
Next, Degawa Reaction Juku...
Asato.
I think I might have figured it out.
Degawa Reaction Juku, followed by...
The Hot King of the Press!
Then, this one that looks the hottest.
Yes, sir.
Are you going to do it?
I'll do it once.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
What's going on?
Wait a minute!
This is bad.
It's too hot!
It's a little too hot.
Okay, Mana-san, here we go.
Here we go.
Okay.
What?
Heart
Yes, I'll go.
Here we go!
What are you doing?
Look at me.
I'm not sure.
You're scaring me!
You're scared, too.
You're gonna get away with it.
So if we do this early in the morning...
I'm scared.
Cheerful, cheery, cheery Mayu-tan!
Nagi-chan, don't hold me back.
You're going to say that?
Of course, otherwise you'd run away, right?
Everyone ran away, didn't they?
It's a shame.
Reaction is a group art.
Based on this, let's do take 2.
Here we go, Ms. Manatsu!
Stop, stop, stop!
Wait, wait, wait.
Mayu-tan, here we go.
Eee... eee...
Oh, wow!
in, in, in
Don't accept it.
Don't accept it, Kakki!
Don't accept it!
I wanted to be a suppressor, so we cackle together!
Yes, yes, yes, yes
Okay, I'll go for the daikon next!
Daikon radish looks so bad!
I'm going for the daikon!
Don't throw it away!
I'm going to get daikon!
Oh, oh, oh!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
What's with that face?
That's new.
I like it.That's nice.
I've never seen you look like that.
It's good. It's good, it's good, it's good.
It's good, isn't it?
Last one, last one.
Eggs! Eggs!
You're stopping, right, Ms. Manatsu?
Here go the eggs!
Hey, don't stop everyone!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Go, go, go, go!
Aaah aaah aaah aaah aaah aaah aaah aaah
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Why are you blowing up?
Why am I doing that?
Akimoto and the members learned the basics of reaction in "Degawa Juku".
Now it's time for car stunts!
I wonder if this will be useful.
Here we are at the car stunt place!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Finally here we are at the car stunt site
Everything from explosives to cranes is already on standby
I said I wanted to do it, but I'm scared.
Do you understand, Ms. Manatsu, when you see this car stunt?
Do you feel something different about that one?
There's a camera and a belt on top.
Oh, that's right.
That's what I mean.
Me, Ryu and Ega-chan are on a higher level
I'm often made to ride on top of this.
I've never seen a girl on top of this.
That's amazing.
Akimoto's challenge this time is...
Akimoto's challenge this time is to do a car stunt on the roof of a car, which is outside of the car and more dangerous than ever.
Akimoto's wish for the success of his new song and the growth of Nogizaka.
The last challenge was to ride on the car and do a kusuda (car stunt).
Can I ask you to help me with that?
Of course, of course!
There's a hook attached to the crane truck.
That's where you hook the cusdama.
Can you do that role, Mr. Degawa?
Yes, of course.
Mr. Degawa, you'll be riding on top of this.
I'd like you to get on top of it and hook it.
I'd really like it if you could do it.
Before you do it, Ms. Manatsu.
I'll get on top of it and go for the hook.
I see.
What do you mean?
I'd like to see Izukawa-san do it, too.
I'll set up the kusudama for later.
I'm going to ask the legendary Izukawa to show us his reaction to the car stunts.
Give your best pass to Ms. Manatsu.
I'll do it. Wait for me, Ms. Manatsu.
Good luck, Mr. Degawa.
Anytime, please.
Behold the life of the legendary Izukawa, with 38 years of experience in the art form.
He's early! He's early!
Wow!
I'm so happy!
Oh, oh, oh!
YEAH!
The members were worried about the legend's health due to the intensity of the event, but then Izukawa spoke up and said...
Aaah!
Ahh!
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
Same 2
There is no ...
Oh!
It's gonna explode!
After they make you do all this.
They'll give you a couple of cooze balls.
I've got the cous-balls for Akimoto safely set up.
And set it up.
The job was supposed to be over.
I'm scared.
Wow!
Wah!
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared
I think it's coming through here.
Wow.
Yay.
Thank you very much.
Degawa, who passed the baton to Akimoto X Tama, is waiting for the other members to join him.
Hey, you guys, talk.
Are you okay?
I told you so.
React as a group.
I'm sorry. I told you.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
If someone does something, I'll run to ask if they're okay.
Forty-six.I read 46.
I have a runny nose. Are you okay?
I have a runny nose. I'm fine. I'm not kidding.
Runny nose is a tire moon for a comedian.
Camera, please.
Excuse me...
Is this really expensive?
It's more money than a small show.
I'm sure it cost a fortune.
I couldn't make it to graduation.
You'll get a lot of it. We'll graduate at the next show.
We'll pay you from there.
Akimoto is finally standing by to take Degawa's baton. Can he pull off the difficult car stunt?
Mana-san, are you ready?
If this happens, we're going to die.
Akimoto, are you okay? We're going to die.
Good luck.
Bye.
Good bye.
Akimoto, the man who decided to take on the stamp challenge...
Akimoto, who's a super herself, decided to take on the stamp challenge... and perform even tougher stunts than Dessert did.
I wonder if he'll be okay.
Oh no!
Oh, no!
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Oh, shit.
good luck malacca
go for it!
Hang in there.
You've got him.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God!
They're yelling! They're yelling! They're yelling!
Yeah!
Yay!
It's like...
It's Sanada-san or someone.
I can't tell
Come on, let's go from here. Let's go from here.
Is it still there? Is it still there?
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
Wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah-wah.
Wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah.
Hot, hot, hot.
We're a long way from home.
Wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah
We managed to get through four blasts in a row, despite the hot air.
The only thing left is the Kusudama that Degawa set up.
Pull the string and crack it open, and you're all clear!
I'm definitely going to catch this!
Hang in there, Mr. Naraku!
He'll catch it!
Will he catch it?
Ha-ha-ha!
Cracking the Kusudama from the top of a moving car.
Nogizaka's period of development succeeded beautifully
And then...
Wow!
Wow.
Cool.
It's cool.
How was it?
I was so scared.
No, no, no, no. I'm crying.
Gentlemen, I'm so relieved that you're all here.
Oh, unfortunately, you have a runny nose.
But it's no use. It doesn't come out that easily all of a sudden.
No, no, no, but I'd say this is a pass already, Tanachi-San
The location shoot is over after receiving a pass from the adored Izukawa.
But what was it supposed to be?
I have a sense of accomplishment, but since we're praying for a hit, can't we do something more?
But since we're praying for a hit, can't we do something more?
You mean more intense activities?
Yes, for Nogizaka's hit anyway.
How greedy are you?
But that was great.
More than that?
Takahashi, are you okay with another version?
We'll just have to go in there.
A more intense version.
Like what we used to do in real life.
That one?
The borderline of a reaction comedian.
Akimoto, who entered the Reactors' Cup
At her own request, she tried an even more dangerous car stunt in a hurry.
Well, Ms. Manatsu really wanted to do it a little more, so we did it.
I wonder what it was...
It's totally different.
I was thinking... everyone's different...
Manatsu-san
I've never seen anything like that before
Hang in there.Go for it.
This must be dangerous.
What a high level and super dangerous start for Akimoto Naid too!
Wow!
What?
Seriously?
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
What?
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
Oh, no.
What's with all the avalabone and stuff?
Slip.
What the hell?
A very dangerous stunt in Japan, where a car drags you along at high speed.
Akimoto pulled it off on the spur of the moment.
He did it on the spur of the moment.
So fast!
Scary!
And then he got into the car.
For more stunts.
How hard can you go?
Oh, man.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, that's it!
Seino
Harukun! Turn turn!
You're falling apart!
Whoa! Back, back, back, back!
That's great, that's great, that's great!
That's great!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Wow!
Shake, shake, shake!
Wow!
That's what you wanted to do.
It's a long one. And that Mannerstars version.
Maybe this is what they're saying. I'm very scared.
You know what I'm really scared of? That table.
That table? It was covered with cloth just now.
After this, there's a shocking incident.
For the weak of heart, be warned.
I'm very scared of that table.
What's it for?
Does it fly?
The challenge after this is to run on one wheel using this platform.
If you don't control your center of gravity.
If you don't control your center of gravity, you'll go into a tailspin, which is a deadly stunt that leads to the third degree.
I'm afraid you'll have to do that, too.
A life-threatening stunt that even Degawa would be scared of
Will Akimoto succeed and make it back alive?
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
Are you on it? This...
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaand the end of Etauger.
What?
The car was supposed to be a Catalinian, but it lost its balance and sped up to a major speed bump.
The car spun around and was arrested for stun and failure.
Tension mounts at the scene as staff rushes to the scene of the unexpected accident.
Come here a minute!
Did the door close?
Actually, it's a lot of catalins...
Oh, that's right! It won't open!
But... it's all sticky now... They're doing it after all, aren't they?
Something to cut? With this? Maybe we should call an ambulance.
The fallout from the overturned, dented car is trapped in the car.
Then the door finally opens and DeGar rushes in.
Hey, Banser!
Oh, look out, look out, are you okay?
The members, pale from the unexpected situation, are also self-aware.
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
Whoa! Wow!
You did it!
You scared me!
Oh, my God!
Oh, thank God!
Tête-à-tête.
Whose song is this?
Surprise.
You wanted me to do it.
Oh, wait a minute.
I cried.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Why are you crying?
I thought you were dead.
Stop it!
I'm sorry!
It's the Tête-à-tête song!
Oh, my God!
I'm crying.
How are you crying?
Oh, my God, everyone's crying.
This sequence of events was designed to make the audience think that the stunt had failed, but in fact, they were all right.
Akimoto's homage to the comedy shows of the past.
I see.
Akimoto, before the rollover.
Akimoto ejected from the car just as it entered a square moment before it overturned.
and then quickly made up for the explosion.Then a quick explosion makeup
Finally, he appeared with a promise.
But it was supposed to end with a good laugh.
But the members took it more seriously than expected
and unexpectedly ended up in tears.
Manatsu-san, you really wanted to do this at the end, didn't you?
Yes, I knew that when I said "Can stunt"...
I've always wanted to do it up to this point.
I was so surprised.
What should I do?
What are you doing?
Surprised?
I'm surprised.
You're all right.
Maybe it was a little too real.
It was too real.
Are you crying already?
Why did you call an ambulance?
I thought I was going to die.
That was an ad-lib.
I was good, wasn't I?
I was good.
It was supposed to be the Katakuri method.
You did that?
I didn't.
I really didn't.
How did you like it?
I'm very satisfied.
You made me cry.
From now on, Manatsu will have to compete on her own.
Of course, the Nogizaka members and I will be watching and cheering for you.
Please do your best.
Thank you very much.
Good luck.
So this is what Akimoto wanted to do.
Yes, it's not so much that I want to do something tough, but rather that I want to challenge myself.
If you try something even if it's impossible, you'll see a lot more than you expected.
I wanted to tell the younger students that if you try something even if it's impossible, you can see a lot more than you thought you could.
That's right.
I wonder what they thought when they were shown this.
How was Yuki?
There are a lot of mysteries in this world.
But I've learned to take everything in stride.
Am I right? Not at all.
The beginning, the end, everything's different.
It's been a long time since I've told anyone about this.
Did Matsuo get anything from this part?
He was so confident when he was surrounded by sand and stuff.
Hit by a car.
That's the wrong part.
That's Akimoto. He got run over.
Suzuki, you're the closest.
They've spent so many years together, and what did they receive?
The limit.
Just a little ahead of the limit... you won't die after all.
You won't die after all?
I think it's more like he was trying to convey this to me.
"Don't accept hot oden... once.
Is that so?
That's for Mr. Dev'Reaux's office.
So it has nothing to do with custard.
The title of the 32nd single is...
"Hito wa Yume wo Taisetsumu" (People See Their Dreams Twice).
Mobile selection for Ayane Suzuki's graduation ceremony has started.
Come on, and next time Akimoto Manatsu Grand Finale
I'm Akiharuka... and I'll draw lots.
Oh!
A handball!
Yeah, yeah...
Mwah!
Please subscribe to our channel!